(Sheldon:)Three thousand hours.
(Sheldon:)Three thousand hours
clicking on that mouse,
(Sheldon:)collecting weapons and gold.
(Sheldon:)It's almost as if it was
a huge waste of time.
(Howard:)Whoever did this
knew what they were doing.
(Howard:)He got in and out
of your account in under
(Howard:)15 minutes, transferred
all your stuff,
(Howard:)and didn't leave
a digital fingerprint.
(Sheldon:)Oh!
(Sheldon:)There isn't enough
chamomile tea in the world
(Sheldon:)to quell the rage in my heart.
(Raj:)Hold on. I'm talking to an orc
(Raj:)under the bridge
in Thunder Bluff
(Raj:)who says if we pay him, he'll
help us track down your things.
(Sheldon:)Can we trust him?
I should say so;
he appears to be a member
(Raj:)of the Nigerian royal family.
(Howard:)Whoa! Somebody's auctioning off
a jeweled ostrich bridle!
(Sheldon:)No. Glenn's was leather.
(Sheldon:)He was a simple ostrich.
(Sheldon:)Is! Is, I haven't given up hope.
(Sheldon:)Hey.
(Leonard:)Hey, Penny. We're kind of in
the middle of a crisis, here.